spikesgamezone.com 2016-11-18

# Privacy Policy for Coolmath-Games.com

Effective Date: May 20, 2014 (last updated April 22, 2016)

This Policy describes how we treat personal information on the websites where it is located. This Policy does not apply to other Coolmath.com, LLC websites or apps, such as coolmath4kids.com.

**Information Collected**

For example, we - or vendors we work with - may collect information about our visitor's web browsers. We might look at what sites visitors came from, or what sites visitors go to when they leave. We often do this in order to analyze our web traffic in order to make improvements to our site.

We may use, or allow third parties to use, tracking tools like browser cookies and web beacons. To learn more about these tools and how you can control them, click here.

**Analysis of Coolmath Traffic**

We use information to respond to your requests or questions. For example, we might use your information to respond to your feedback.

We use information to improve our products and services. We may use your information to make our website and services better. We might use your information to customize your experience with us.

We use information for security purposes. We may use information to protect our company, our visitors, and our websites.

We use information to communicate with you about our relationship. We may contact you about your feedback. We might also contact you about this Policy or our website terms.

If you subscribe to our subscriber-only content, we collect information, such as your name, address, username, password and payment card information, in order to provide you the subscription services you request and to process your payments.  

We use information as otherwise permitted by law.

**Sharing of Information**

We will share information with third parties who perform services on our behalf. For example, we may share information with a vendor who conducts a satisfaction survey on our behalf, in order to improve our site. As another example, we share information with a third party not affiliated with us to process subscription payments of our subscribers. 

We will share information if we think we have to in order to comply with the law or to protect ourselves. For example, we will share information to respond to a court order or subpoena. We may share it if a government agency or investigatory body requests. We might share information when we are investigating potential fraud.

We may share information with any successor to all or part of our business.

We may share information for other reasons we may describe to you.

**Your Choices About Sharing and Marketing Practices**

You can control certain cookies and tracking tools. To learn how to manage how we - and our vendors - use cookies and other tracking tools, please click here.

This site and children. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or legal guardian and think your child under 13 has given us information, you can email us at

You can also write to us at the address listed at the end of this policy. Please mark your inquiries "COPPA Information Request." Parents, to learn more about how to protect children's privacy on-line, [click here](http://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0031-protecting-your-childs-privacy-online).

**Security**

The Internet is not 100% secure. We cannot promise that your use of our sites will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. We keep personal information as long as it is necessary or relevant for the practices described in this Policy. We also keep information as otherwise required by law.

**Links to Other Sites**

If you click on a link to a third party site, you will be taken to websites we do not control. This policy does not apply to the privacy practices of that website. Read the privacy policy of other websites carefully. We are not responsible for these third party sites. Our site may also serve third party content that contains their own cookies or tracking technologies. To learn more, click here. We do not control the use of those technologies.

**Questions or Concerns**

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy, please email us at

You can also write to us or call at: Coolmath-games.com, LLC, Attn: Legal Department, 122 East 42nd Street, Suite 1611, New York, NY 10168, or call us at

**Policy Changes**

From time to time we may change our privacy policies. We will notify you of any material changes to our Policy as required by law. We will also post an updated copy on our website. Please check our site periodically for updates.
